Svitlana Myrna Technical Program Manager

Email: sv.myrna@gmail.com Phone: 425.439.9734 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/svitlana-myrna-94024185 Address: Mountlake Terrace, 98043

SUMMARY:

Program Manager with 7 years of experience in leading multiple operational and development projects. Expert in the implementation of engineering solutions for e-commerce web design and development, optimizing the complete software development lifecycle (mobile applications), launch and executing purchasing campaigns under a credit line from EBRD and World Bank.

Interested in program management responsibilities at a company where developer engagement, technical acuity, and efficiency matter.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Technologies: SCRUM/Agile, Waterfall, Six Sigma methodologies, SCRUM, MS SQL, SDLC, security and compliance processes, HTML.

Tools: Jira, Confluence, Asana, MS Azure DevOps, Microsoft office suite, MIRO, FIGMA, SmartDraw, Lucid Chart, AWS, Google.

EXPERIENCE:

Program Manager TemplarSoft, IT e-commerce, mobile applications 2021- 2022

- Increased number of new retailers in the marketplace by 15% in creating and integrating features as a product manager in e-commerce project (warehouse management).
- Gained a new customer category (age +65) in an e-medical mobile application by directing a project for the registration flow update.
- Reached extra 20% return customers and led to 27% profit in 3 months to the e-commerce project by establishing CRM system.
- Launched 2 e-medical mobile applications within 1 year through tight collaboration with team.

Project Manager Naftogaz of Ukraine, Energy Resources

2015 - 2021

- Gained growth of energy commodity client sector from 3 to 40 local and international clients in 4
 years by leading compliance and onboard projects.
- Led efficiency in inventory management structure and reduced costs by 14% saving \$168K per year in logistics (booking capacities) by designing and refactoring on-premise ERP system.
- Reached online trading activity (purchase and sale) instead of physical client's search by reorganizing planning method and started to use trade platform.
- Implemented international standard practice in the Ukrainian energy market by composing a full cycle of agreement management.

Business Analyst EastOne LLC, Financial Investment

2014 - 2015

- Developed HR processes by designing, testing, and deployment successfully corporate online portal.
- Decreased costs by 15% while supporting the same number of clients by implementing cut-off strategy execution.

Project Manager ERTE Trading SA, Trading

2012 - 2013

- Launched and landed start-up commodity trading project by setting up business plan.
- Established functioning subsidiary on the European market by completing registration procedures with state bodies.

EDUCATION:

Post Graduate Diploma in Administration, Business Glion Institute of Higher Education Administration, and Management, General

Geneva, Switzerland

Master of Finance Management in Business Industry, State Economic University of Ukraine, Business Administration and Management, General

Kyiv, Ukraine

Master of Engineering MEng, Nuclear/Nuclear Power National Technical University of Technology, Technician

Ukraine, Kyiv, Ukraine

CERTIFICATION:

- Google Project Management Coursera
- Business Analysis LABA
- EFET legal Masterclass on Master Trading Agreements Correggio Consulting
- Maintaining the functioning of the integrated management system TMS sp2019/04-7977

VOLUNTEERING:

April 22-October 22.

Volunteered as a project manager and a low code engineer across several start-up and non-profit organizations:

- Designed and implemented a refugee assistance website that provided critical information to more than 2000 Ukrainian refugees in WA state.
- Developed a vaccination promotion website that received a 10K grant from the WA State Department of Health
- Initiated and planned a project that led to an agreement concluded for a project of +\$100k budget.
- Designed and successfully deployed a childcare website that gained +4 new attendees within 2 months.